<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on Sustainable Fisheries Group</title>
    <link>/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on Sustainable Fisheries Group</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Juan Mayorga</title>
      <link>/about/juan-mayorga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/juan-mayorga/</guid>
      <description>Juan grew up in Bogota, Colombia, were he received his bachelor’s degree in environmental engineering with minors in biology and management from the Universidad de Los Andes. After completing his undergraduate degree, he received a prestigious scholarship to participate in the Sea Education Association Semester program. In this role he analyzed suitable tuna habitat in the Central Pacific Ocean while living aboard a sailing vessel. Since then, Juan has applied interdisciplinary science to a wide array of marine science and conservation problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kat Millage</title>
      <link>/about/kat-millage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/kat-millage/</guid>
      <description>Originally from Portland, Oregon, Kat received a BA in biochemistry with a minor in environmental science from the University of San Diego. After completing her undergraduate degree, she worked in pharmaceutical development for a short time before moving to the Turks and Caicos Islands to pursue her interest in the marine environment. During this time, she conducted monitoring surveys as part of fishery assessments for conch and lobster, which led her to return to graduate school to learn more about fisheries and coastal management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sustainable Fisheries Group (SFG)</title>
      <link>/about/sfg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/sfg/</guid>
      <description>SFG was founded in 2006 by marine ecologist Steve Gaines and economist Chris Costello and is a collaboration between the Marine Science Institute and the Bren School of Environmental Science and Management. SFG develops innovative science and applies it to real-world challenges to improve the sustainability of marine resources and coastal communities. SFG utilizes diverse market approaches, bioeconomic modeling, and spatial analysis to improve the ecological and economic performance of fisheries and other ocean uses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tyler Clavelle</title>
      <link>/about/tyler-clavelle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/tyler-clavelle/</guid>
      <description>Tyler received his BA as a double major in Biology and Economics from Bucknell University in 2009. Following graduation, he spent two years working as the assistant manager of the Bimini Biological Field Station, a shark research lab in Bimini, Bahamas. After developing an interest in science and policy intersections, Tyler returned to graduate school and earned his Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in coastal marine resource management from the Bren School of Environmental Science and Management at UCSB.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>