<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sfg on Sustainable Fisheries Group</title>
    <link>/tags/sfg/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sfg on Sustainable Fisheries Group</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 13:50:46 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/sfg/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Staff Resources</title>
      <link>/blog/staff_resources/staff_resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2018 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/staff_resources/staff_resources/</guid>
      <description>Introduction R/RStudio Installation Packages  Github Installation  Gmail &amp;amp; Google Calendar Box Slack   Introduction Here at SFG we use numerous programs and platforms to organize, collaborate, and conduct our research. While we recognize that everyone has a workflow that works for them, we want to make sure everyone is familiar with the tools we use and how to get the most out of them in your own workflows and project management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SFG Looks to the Sky to Understand the Sea</title>
      <link>/blog/under-the-sea/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/under-the-sea/</guid>
      <description>In June, SFG team members Tyler Clavelle, Grant McDermott, and Juan Mayorga traveled to Palo Alto, California to participate in the 2017 User Summit for Google’s Earth Engine (GEE), a planetary-scale platform for earth science data and analysis. GEE is transforming geospatial research by enabling scientists to ask and answer questions at scales that have never before been possible. Since it’s inception in 2010, researchers have used GEE for hundreds of groundbreaking studies and applications, such as mapping global forest cover, surface water, and malaria risk, in high-resolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working toward a sustainable future in the Eastern Caribbean</title>
      <link>/blog/sustainable-future-caribbean/sustainable-future-caribbean/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/sustainable-future-caribbean/sustainable-future-caribbean/</guid>
      <description>SFG has been working with the Blue Halo Initiative since 2014, and my field visits to Montserrat and Antigua and Barbuda showed me just how diverse the Initiative’s sites and programs really are. My guide and companion for my two-week trip was Andy Estep, the Waitt Institute’s Science &amp;amp; Field Manager, who has lived and worked in the Caribbean for several years.
We began in Antigua, where we met with Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>